Welcome to the Amazon Business Seller Series Negotiated Pricing Module.
After watching this video, you'll understand the importance of the Negotiated Pricing
feature and how to manage it on your site.
Amazon Business Sellers, who have negotiated pricing with a specific customer, can now
upload that pre-arranged agreement to their account.
This enables the seller to manage customer-specific pricing, upload new file versions, and edit
outdated pricing.
Before you start uploading a negotiated price file, be sure to reach out to your customer
and obtain their business ID number.
This will be needed in the following steps.
Once you have the business ID, log in to Seller Central and click on Pricing and then
Negotiated Pricing.
Click on the Add Customer button and then enter the buyer's business ID and click Search.
Once you've found the correct business, select Add Customer.
Now that your customer has been successfully added, you can now add the negotiated price
file by clicking on Upload Price Sheet.
You may browse for a file that's ready or you can download a blank template to start
a new file.
In step 2 of adding a price file, enter the price sheet description, start date, and end
date.
Once complete, select Upload Price Sheet.
You'll notice that your entry will show "in progress" which indicates that we're processing
the file.
Upon successfully processing, it transitions to "Awaiting customer approval."
Once the customer approves all pricing, please allow 24 hours for the pricing to post to
your account.
This concludes the negotiated pricing module of the Amazon Business Seller Series.
Thank you for tuning in.